PATTHARAPON BOONMA

Mobile: +66 (0)909243237 Linkin: Pattharapon Boonma Email: Pattharapon.boo@dome.tu.ac.th

Reside: Petchaburi, Thailand



Profile

An experience in office coordinator and assistants with a background of a JFCCT(Joint Foreign Chambers of commerce in Thailand) intern. Good command over English Thai and Indonesian (reading/Speaking/Writing). Strong in interpersonal, problem-solving and fast-learning skill. Have an ability to work without supervision. Adhere to can-do attitude and lifelong learning. strong background in Southeast Asian academic fields, especially Indonesia and graduated with a research named Coronavirus2019: Pandemic Transmission, consequences and Indonesia's measurement

Education

Thammasat University (2017-2021)

Bachelor of Liberal Arts, major in Southeast Asian studies

GPA:3.58 (First-class honors) *Finished Reserved Officers' training Corps Course since high school.

Experience

Office coordinator, executive and research assistance (Internship), 2020 Joint Foreign Chambers of commerce in Thailand

- summarize economic document to report SME committee report and conduct numerous researches to accommodate the booklet for Webinar: Support Measures for Economic Recovery, joined with Board of Investment (BOI).
- work with several JFCCT committees, especially, SME and Digital economy committees to assist with their various tasks.
- support working team holding online minutes and conference among the Chambers of commerce via Zoom and sum up.
- participate courtesy visit in Spain, Japan, French, China and Thailand's chambers of commerce in Thailand and perform the impact of Covid-19 surveys to advice government measures.

Thai-Indonesian Interpreter (Freelance), 2018 - present

Translated English Thai and Indonesian for clients and professors in papers and meeting

- Translate Thai-Indonesian and Indonesian-Thai documents including to short-long textbooks, news, governmental documents, regulations, minutes summaries and so on. However, English is available service as well. Have no experienced to work as professional interpreter but even so be able to supervise and look after many groups of Indonesians as a student supporter.

Document arrangement's staff (Part-time), 2017 - 2019

Provided and rearranged the significant document of notable professor in Thammasat University Library.

Extracurricular Activity & Achievement

Thammasat university ASEAN Delegation, Oct 2018 - 19

A Thammasat university representative, cooperate with the ASEAN regional universities.

Cultural exchange summer program, June - July 2019

- Participated the cultural and language summer program in Universitas Gadjah Mada, Indonesia for 2 months and graduated with GPA: 4.00 in each of Intermediate levels.

Indonesian exchanged student's supporter, Aug 2017 – 2020

- Facilitated the Indonesian exchange or internship student and arrange the events, activities and workshop

Miscellaneous

Language: Thai (Native), English (fluent), Indonesia (Communicable)

Computer Skill: strong using in Microsoft office's team, Apple's Ecosystem, Photoshop Ae and Ai, and Davinci video editor program.